<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Definitely Not a Robot</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Definitely Not a Robot</description>

         
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Privacy Policy</title>
                    <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                    <description>Privacy Policy Last Updated: November 13, 2025&#xA;This Privacy Policy describes how Definitely Not a Robot (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) collects, uses, and discloses your information when you use our website and services (the &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;).&#xA;1. Information We Collect We only collect information that you voluntarily provide to us when you interact with our website, primarily through our contact form.&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Terms of Use</title>
                    <link>http://localhost:1313/terms-of-use/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                    <description>Terms and Conditions Last Updated: November 13, 2025&#xA;Please read these Terms of Use (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) carefully before using the Definitely Not a Robot website and services (the &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;) operated by Definitely Not a Robot.&#xA;1. Acceptance of Terms By accessing and using the Service, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you disagree with any part of the terms, then you may not access the Service.&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Accessibility Statement</title>
                    <link>http://localhost:1313/accessibility-statement/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
                    <description>Accessibility Statement We are committed to making our website content and experience accessible and user-friendly for everyone. We strive to provide a positive experience for all visitors, regardless of ability or the adaptive technology being used.&#xA;Conformance Status The Definitely Not a Robot website strives to conform with Level AA of the World Wide Web Consortium’s (W3C) Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) 2.1.&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
                
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
